

# **Motakabbir Hossan**

Bhawal Jamalpur - 1723, Kaliganj, Gazipur, Dhaka contact@motakabbir.com www.motakabbir.com @m0takabbir

Dedicated graphic Designer with three years of experience in adobe Suite, and in managing challenging problem solving. Eager to join creative team to share expert knowledge in digital and new media, and graphic design. In the meantime to learn from the team.

## **SKILLS AND PROFICIENCIES**

- Art history concepts, ageappropriate lessons, classroom management
- Graphic design software, painting techniques
- Creative thinking, effective communications, leadership, teamwork, time management

# **WORKSHOPS AND COURSES**

Graphic Design University of Colorado September 2020

Korean Language Yonsie University March 2021

Learning Linux
The Linux Foundation - EDX
July 2021

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Admin of techSMSBD Tech solution Website(August 201 6 - Present)

Playing the successful role of admin of techSMSBD for 5 years.
 Generate new ideas as well as give the direction to create exclusive content Facilitates discussions on aesthetic concepts and art appreciation. Demonstrates creative techniques in creating new and aesthetic designs for the website.

### Freelancer

Graphic Design (July 2017 - Present)

 Discussed business objectives and project requirements with each client. Applied creativity in designing eye-catching visuals.
 Supervised printing, production, and publishing of client-approved output.

## Creative Content Writer - Intern

Glorious Bangladesh (August 2021 - October 2021)

– Communicated with and wrote creative and user-friendly content. Collaborated with other creative professionals team management and team instructor. Used a wide array of research including google and other social media platform.

# **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

Electrical and Electronics Engineering Shyamoli Textile Engineering College - University of Dhaka Mohammadpur, Dhaka 2020-2024

Science National Ideal College Khilgaon, Dhaka 2017-2019